<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mission Control on strandedinspace</title>
    <link>https://strandedinspace.info/tags/mission-control/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mission Control on strandedinspace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 08:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://strandedinspace.info/tags/mission-control/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This one won&#39;t fit - She&#39;s too flamboyant!</title>
      <link>https://strandedinspace.info/mission-control/this-one-wont-fit-shes-too-flamboyant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://strandedinspace.info/mission-control/this-one-wont-fit-shes-too-flamboyant/</guid>
      <description>Here at Mission Control, we&amp;rsquo;re constantly thinking about the comfort of our cosmonauts. We try to accommodate their dietary restrictions (all you can eat shrimp buffet always tops the list), flight path preferences (#509-191 just had to see the Great Wall of China on his way up), and wardrobe changes. But when it comes to our fleet&amp;rsquo;s mechanical equipment, safety is our paramount priority. FC#516-818 posed a special dilemma this week, as her space suit was so large and delicate that our standard shuttles couldn&amp;rsquo;t contain her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aliens ...</title>
      <link>https://strandedinspace.info/mission-control/on-aliens/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://strandedinspace.info/mission-control/on-aliens/</guid>
      <description>On 05-03-2020 our intrepid travelers encountered an anomaly in the fabric of space-time. We here at Mission Control do not speculate on that which cannot be proven. Instead, we will let our readers explore their own conclusions; but before the fringe starts losing their shit on Twitter, we encourage all to remember that our cosmonauts are technically alien in their current location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Travel is Treacherous</title>
      <link>https://strandedinspace.info/mission-control/space-travel-is-treacherous/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://strandedinspace.info/mission-control/space-travel-is-treacherous/</guid>
      <description>Mission Control received a downlink transmission on 5-4-2020 reporting sweeping losses in Cosmonaut 501-639&amp;rsquo;s payload. It is going to take significant time to rectify this loss and unravel the Five W&amp;rsquo;s remotely. Our team is scrambling to send a Zoologist to join the gang, we hadn&amp;rsquo;t anticipated needing such a specialist, but now the question looms heavy: Are there deer or rabbits in space?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flowers in Space</title>
      <link>https://strandedinspace.info/mission-control/flowers-in-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://strandedinspace.info/mission-control/flowers-in-space/</guid>
      <description>Helen Sharman is AMAZING! She was the first British astronaut and the first woman to visit MIR Space Station! A chemist, Sharman accompanied Sergei Krikalev on the Soyuz TM-12 as a Research Cosmonaut at only 27 years old, and she brought along a bag of 25,000 pansy seeds to test their subjectivity to cosmic radiation.
Flamingo Cosmonaut 501-639 is proud to be nicknamed after Sharman, and embarked upon her journey into outer space with a Cadmium Yellow Medium colored Ranunculus plant on her back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Production</title>
      <link>https://strandedinspace.info/mission-control/production/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://strandedinspace.info/mission-control/production/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
